Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXXIX. RULES
  - Sub-Series 279-79. Rules. Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad Company
    - Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad Company, 1930-1944 (Box 362, Folder 16)
    - Case No. A-3931, 1951-1953 (Box 362, Folder 17)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 362, Folder 18)
    - Agreements (Box 362, Folder 19)
      not dated.
    - Kentucky and Indiana Terminal Railroad Company, 1921 (Box 362, Folder 20)
    - Case No. A-2179, 1945-1946 (Box 363, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 279-80. Rules. Kansas City, Mexico, and Orient Railroad Company
    - Kansas City, Mexico, and Orient Railroad Company, 1921 (Box 363, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 279-81. Rules. Kansas City Southern Railway Company
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 363, Folder 3)
    - General, 1957-1962 (Box 363, Folder 4)
    - 1959 Vacation and Holiday Movement (Box 363, Folder 5)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 363, Folder 6)
    - General, 1950-1956 (Box 363, Folder 7)
      July 1950-56.
    - Rules Revision. Mediation Case No. A-4845, 1955-1956 (Box 363, Folder 8)
    - Mediation Case No. R-2548, 1951-1956 (Box 363, Folder 9)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 363, Folder 10)
    - Kansas City Southern Railway Company, 1945-1950 (Box 363, Folder 11)
      1945-June 1950.
    - Kansas City Southern Railway Company, 1938-1944 (Box 363, Folder 12)
    - Vacations, 1943-1948 (Box 363, Folder 13)
    - Kansas City Southern Railway Company, 1930-1937 (Box 363, Folder 14)
    - Kansas City Southern Railway Company, 1935 (Box 363, Folder 15)
    - Kansas City Southern Railway Company, 1933 (Box 363, Folder 16)
    - Kansas City Southern Railway Company, 1922-1927 (Box 363, Folder 17)
    - Kansas City Southern Railway Company, 1921-1922 (Box 364, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 279-82. Rules. Florida East Coast Railway Company
    - 279-82 (Section 2). Rules Revision. Mediation Case No. A-6654, 1962 (Box 364, Folder 2)
      April 1962-July 18, 1962.
    - 279-82 (Section 1). Rules Revision. Mediation Case No. A-6654, 1960-1962 (Box 364, Folder 3)
      1960-March 1962.
    - General, 1948-1962 (Box 364, Folder 4)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 364, Folder 5)
    - Mediation Case No. C-2873, 1958-1959 (Box 364, Folder 6)
    - Veterans' Vacation. Mediation Case No. C-2418, 1954-1957 (Box 364, Folder 7)
    - Agreements, 1946-1949 (Box 364, Folder 8)
    - 279-82 (Section 2). 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 364, Folder 9)
    - Vacations, 1942-1947 (Box 364, Folder 10)
    - 279-82 (a). Florida East Coast Railway Company, 1941-1947 (Box 364, Folder 11)
    - Panel Board Proceedings, 1946 (Box 364, Folder 12-13)
      May 28, 1946-June 8, 1946.
    - 279-82 (a). Florida East Coast Railway Company, 1930-1940 (Box 364, Folder 14)
    - Florida East Coast Railway Company, 1926-1928 (Box 364, Folder 15)
    - Florida East Coast Railway Company, 1921-1922 (Box 364, Folder 16)
    - Union Shop, 1953-1954 (Box 365, Folder 1)
    - Mediation Case No. A-3916, 1951-1956 (Box 365, Folder 2)
    - Case No. A-3985, 1952 (Box 365, Folder 3)
    - 279-82 (Section 2). 40-Hour Week, 1949-1950 (Box 365, Folder 4)
    - Case No. A-1129, 1942-1947 (Box 365, Folder 5)
    - Statements and Exhibits. Case No. A-1129, 1946 (Box 365, Folder 6-7)
    - 279-82 (a). Cases Nos. A-404 and A-1132, 1938-1946 (Box 365, Folder 8)
    - Case No. A-2152, 1945-1946 (Box 365, Folder 9)
    - Job Protection Agreement. Case No. A-609, 1939 (Box 365, Folder 10)
    - National Mediation Board Election, 1937 (Box 365, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-83. Rules. Duluth and Iron Range Railroad
    - Duluth and Iron Range Railroad, 1921 (Box 365, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 279-84. Rules. Missouri Pacific Railroad Company
    - Arbitration Cases Nos. A-1554 and A-1627, 1946 (Box 365, Folder 13)
      1946 June 28
    - Case No. A-1627. Carrier's Exhibits, 1945 (Box 365, Folder 14)
    - Case No. A-1627.Saturday Afternoons, 1945 (Box 365, Folder 15)
    - Arbitration Hearing. Case No. A-1627, 1946 (Box 365, Folder 16)
      June 24-26, 1946.
    - Arbitration Proceedings. Cases Nos. A-1554 and A-1627, 1945 (Box 365, Folder 17)
      August 13-16, 1945.
    - Arbitration Case No. A-1554. Carrier's Exhibits, 1945 (Box 365, Folder 18)
    - Arbitration Case No. A-1554. Grand Lodge File. Weighing of Cases, 1945 (Box 365, Folder 19)
    - Mediation Cases Nos. A-6782 and C-3245, 1962-1963 (Box 366, Folder 1)
    - Appeal. Imes, M.L. Lodge No. 284, 1960-1961 (Box 366, Folder 2)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6467, 1960-1961 (Box 366, Folder 3)
    - 7-Day Warehouse Operation, St. Louis, Missouri. Mediation Case No. A-5247, 1956-1957 (Box 366, Folder 4)
    - Veterans' Vacation. Mediation Case No. C-2418, 1954-1957 (Box 366, Folder 5)
    - Case No. A-4098, 1952-1953 (Box 366, Folder 1)
    - Case No. A-3034, 1948-1952 (Box 366, Folder 2)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1949-1958 (Box 366, Folder 3)
    - 279-84 (Section 3). 40-Hour Week, 1949-1950 (Box 366, Folder 4)
      September 24, 1949-50.
    - 279-84 (Section 2). 40-Hour Week, 1949 (Box 366, Folder 5)
      June 1949-September 23, 1949.
    - Exhibits, 1945 (Box 366, Folder 6)
    - Grand Lodge File. Weighing Cars. Case No. A-1627, 1944-1945 (Box 366, Folder 7)
    - 279-84 (Section 1). 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 366, Folder 8)
      1948-May 23, 1949.
    - Vacations, 1942-1949 (Box 366, Folder 9)
    - 279-84 (c). Schedule Revision. Case No. A-1259, 1940-1943 (Box 367, Folder 1)
    - 279-84 (b). Red Caps. Case No. R-585, 1939-1941 (Box 367, Folder 2)
    - 279-84 (c). Red Caps. Case No. C-563, 1930-1932 (Box 367, Folder 3)
    - Agreements, 1938-1942 (Box 367, Folder 4)
    - Case No. A-3244, 1949 (Box 367, Folder 5)
    - Vacation Dispute. Telephone Operators. National Railroad Adjustment Board Award No. 4341, 1948 (Box 367, Folder 6)
    - Vacation Dispute. Batte, G.H., et. al. National Railroad Adjustment Board Award No. 4032, 1944-1947 (Box 367, Folder 7)
    - Rules Dispute. Mediation Board Case No. A-1259. Exhibits A-F, 1942 (Box 367, Folder 8)
    - Weighing of Cars. Case No. A-1554, 1943-1946 (Box 367, Folder 9)
    - Employees' Exhibits. Case No. A-1554, 1945 (Box 367, Folder 10)
    - Extra Exhibits. Case No. A-1554, 1945 (Box 367, Folder 11)
    - Union Shop, 1956-1962 (Box 367, Folder 12)
    - General, 1955-1956 (Box 368, Folder 1)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 368, Folder 2)
    - Rules Revision, 1952 (Box 368, Folder 3)
      March 25, 1952-October 8, 1952.
    - Rules Revision, 1952 (Box 368, Folder 4)
      February 12, 1952-March 24, 1952.
    - Rules Revision, 1951-1952 (Box 368, Folder 5)
      May 1951-February 11, 1952.
    - Rules Revision, 1950-1951 (Box 368, Folder 6)
      1950-April 1951.
    - 279-84 (a). General, 1947-1948 (Box 368, Folder 7)
      March 1947-May 1948.
    - 279-84 (a). General, 1946-1947 (Box 368, Folder 8)
      June 1946-February 1947.
    - 279-84 (a). General, 1944-1946 (Box 368, Folder 9)
      1944-May 1946.
    - 279-84 (a). Missouri Pacific Railroad Company, 1939-1943 (Box 368, Folder 10)
    - General, 1951-1954 (Box 369, Folder 1)
    - General, 1948-1950 (Box 369, Folder 2)
      June 1948-December 1950.
    - 1953 Rules Changes Movement, 1953-1956 (Box 369, Folder 3)
    - Memorandum Agreement, 1939 (Box 369, Folder 4)
    - 279-84 (a). Missouri Pacific Railroad Company, 1932-1938 (Box 369, Folder 5)
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad Company, 1921 (Box 369, Folder 6)
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad Company, 1921-1926 (Box 369, Folder 7)
    - Missouri Pacific Railroad Company, 1921 (Box 369, Folder 8-9)
    - 279-84 (Section 2). Saturday Afternoon. Case No. A-1627, 1946 (Box 369, Folder 10)
      February-August 1946.
    - 279-84 (Section 1). Saturday Afternoon. Case No. A-1627, 1944-1946 (Box 369, Folder 11)
      1944-January 1946.
    - Carrier's Exhibits. Rehearing, Case No. A-1627, 1946 (Box 369, Folder 12)
      1946 June
    - Employees' Exhibits. Case No. A-1627, 1946 (Box 369, Folder 13)
    - General, 1963-1964 (Box 369, Folder 14)
    - General, 1960-1962 (Box 369, Folder 15)
      October 1960-62.
    - General, 1959-1960 (Box 369, Folder 16)
      1959-September 1960.
    - General, 1958 (Box 369, Folder 17)
      May-July 1958.
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 370, Folder 1)
    - General, 1957-1958 (Box 370, Folder 2)
      1957-April 1958.
  - Sub-Series 279-85. Rules. Ann Arbor Railroad Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 370, Folder 3)
    - Mediation Case No. A-5125, 1956 (Box 370, Folder 4)
    - Agreements, 1942-1956 (Box 370, Folder 5)
    - General, 1946-1956 (Box 370, Folder 6)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 370, Folder 7)
    - Vacations, 1942-1949 (Box 370, Folder 8)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Company, 1941-1945 (Box 370, Folder 9)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Company, 1926-1940 (Box 370, Folder 10)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Company, 1921 (Box 370, Folder 11)
    - Ann Arbor Railroad Company, 1937 (Box 370, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 279-86. Rules. Trunk Line Freight Inspection Bureau
    - Trunk Line Freight Inspection Bureau, 1921-1928 (Box 370, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 279-87. Rules. Fort Worth and Denver City Railway
    - 40-Hour Week, 1949-1958 (Box 370, Folder 14)
    - General, 1931-1955 (Box 370, Folder 15)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 370, Folder 16)
    - Case No. A-3269, 1946-1950 (Box 370, Folder 17)
    - 40-Hour Week. Service on Rest Days, 1948-1951 (Box 370, Folder 18)
    - Vacations, 1944-1949 (Box 370, Folder 19)
    - Rules Revision. Case No. A-693, 1938-1947 (Box 370, Folder 20)
    - Fort Worth and Denver City Railway, 1945-1946 (Box 370, Folder 21)
    - Fort Worth and Denver City Railway, 1921-1924 (Box 370, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 279-88. Rules. Indianapolis Union Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 370, Folder 23)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1956 (Box 370, Folder 24)
    - Agreements, 1943 (Box 370, Folder 25)
      1943 January 11
    - General, 1924-1955 (Box 370, Folder 26)
    - Case No. A-1635, 1943-1944 (Box 370, Folder 27)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 370, Folder 28)
    - Case No. A-4468, 1951-1955 (Box 371, Folder 1)
    - Proposed Rules, 1921 (Box 371, Folder 2-4)
    - Vacations, 1942 (Box 371, Folder 5)
    - Indianapolis Union Railway Company, 1921 (Box 371, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 279-89. Rules. Los Angeles and Salt Lake Railroad
    - Los Angeles and Salt Lake Railroad, 1921-1924 (Box 371, Folder 7)
    - Los Angeles and Salt Lake Railroad, 1933-1939 (Box 371, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 279-90. Rules. Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau
    - Representation Case No. R-1586, 1946 (Box 371, Folder 9)
      1946 May
    - 40-Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 371, Folder 10)
    - Vacations, 1949-1951 (Box 371, Folder 11)
    - Case No. A-2924, 1948-1950 (Box 371, Folder 12)
    - Representation Case No. R-1586, 1946 (Box 371, Folder 13)
      March 10, 1946-April 1946.
    - Representation Case No. R-1586, 1946 (Box 371, Folder 14)
      February 20, 1946-March 6, 1946.
    - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau, 1946 (Box 371, Folder 15)
      March 7-9, 1946.
    - Representation Case No. R-1586, 1945-1946 (Box 371, Folder 16)
      1945-February 19, 1946.
    - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau, 1946-1951 (Box 371, Folder 17)
      November 1946-June 1951.
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 372, Folder 1)
    - Mediation Case No. C-3463, 1962-1965 (Box 372, Folder 2)
    - General, 1956-1962 (Box 372, Folder 3)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 372, Folder 4)
    - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau, 1951-1955 (Box 372, Folder 5)
      July 1951-55.
    - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau, 1921-1929 (Box 372, Folder 6)
    - General, 1941-1946 (Box 372, Folder 7)
      1941-October 1946.
    - Western Weighing and Inspection Bureau, 1929-1940 (Box 372, Folder 8)
    - Mediation Case No. A-5501, 1957 (Box 372, Folder 9)
    - Case No. A-4165, 1953-1954 (Box 372, Folder 10)
    - Case No. A-3553, 1950-1951 (Box 372, Folder 11)
    - Rules Revision, 1947-1948 (Box 372, Folder 12)
      March 1947-December 1948.
  - Sub-Series 279-91. Rules. Western Maryland Railway Company
    - General, 1958-1962 (Box 372, Folder 13)
      1958-November 1962.
  - Sub-Series 279-96. Rules. Rutland Railroad
    - Rutland Railroad, 1931-1944 (Box 372, Folder 14)
    - Allocation of Funds. Abandonment, 1963-1964 (Box 372, Folder 15)
    - Allocation of Funds. Abandonment, 1963 (Box 372, Folder 16)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6481, 1960-1963 (Box 373, Folder 1)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 373, Folder 2)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 373, Folder 3)
    - Supplemental Agreement No. 11, 1951 (Box 373, Folder 4)
      1951 July 1
    - Shaw, W. vs. Lodge No. 6043, 1955-1956 (Box 373, Folder 5)
    - General, 1956-1963 (Box 373, Folder 6)
    - General, 1952-1955 (Box 373, Folder 7)
    - General, 1945-1951 (Box 373, Folder 8)
    - Case No. A-3081, 1949 (Box 373, Folder 9)
    - Vacation Case No. A-2051, 1945-1947 (Box 373, Folder 10)
    - Rutland Railroad, 1921-1924 (Box 373, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-97. Rules. Norfolk and Western Railway Company
    - Mediation Case No. A-6307, 1960-1965 (Box 373, Folder 12)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6296, 1960-1964 (Box 373, Folder 13)
    - General -September 1959-1963 (Box 373, Folder 14)
    - Rules Revision, 1952-1956 (Box 373, Folder 15)
      1952-October 1956.
    - Mediation Case No. A-5954, 1958-1961 (Box 373, Folder 16)
    - Mediation Case No. A-4564, 1954-1957 (Box 373, Folder 17)
    - Veterans Vacation. Mediation Case No. C-2418, 1955-1957 (Box 373, Folder 18)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 373, Folder 19)
    - Rules Revision. Mediation Case No. A-5331, 1958-1959 (Box 373, Folder 20)
      October 1958-59.
    - Rules Revision. Mediation Case No. A-5331, 1956-1958 (Box 373, Folder 21)
      1956-October 1958.
    - 279-97 (a). General -1952-August 1959 (Box 374, Folder 1)
    - 279-97 (a). General -1940-1951 (Box 374, Folder 2)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 374, Folder 3)
    - 279-97 (Section 2). 40-Hour Week, 1949-1951 (Box 374, Folder 4)
      August 1949-51.
    - 279-97 (Section 1). 40-Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 374, Folder 5)
      1948-July 1949.
    - Vacations 1944-1948 (Box 374, Folder 6)
    - 279-97 (a). Case No. A-2018, 1941-1947 (Box 374, Folder 7)
    - Rules Revision, 1942-1945 (Box 374, Folder 8)
    - Case No. A-4014, 1952 (Box 374, Folder 9)
    - 1937-1940 (Box 374, Folder 10)
    - General, 1957-1962 (Box 374, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-98. Rules. Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad, 1948-1956 (Box 374, Folder 12)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6470, 1961-1962 (Box 374, Folder 13)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6460, 1960-1962 (Box 374, Folder 14)
    - 1958 Rules Movement, 1958-1959 (Box 374, Folder 15)
    - 40-Hour Week, 1950-1957 (Box 374, Folder 16)
    - Mediation Case No. A-6249, 1960-1962 (Box 374, Folder 17)
    - Mediation Case No. 1961-1962 (Box 374, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 279-63. Rules. Gulf, Mobile, and Northern
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Northern, 1931-1940 (Box 375, Folder 1)
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Northern, 1921-1926 (Box 375, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 279-91. Rules. Western Maryland
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 375, Folder 3)
    - Clerical Forces, 1935 (Box 375, Folder 4-4a)
    - Clerical Forces, 1935 (Box 375, Folder 5)
    - Clerical Forces, 1935 (Box 375, Folder 6)
    - Western Maryland, 1953-1957 (Box 375, Folder 7)
    - Western Maryland, 1945-1952 (Box 375, Folder 8)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 375, Folder 9)
    - R-58, 1934-1945 (Box 375, Folder 10-10a)
    - Western Maryland, 1921 (Box 375, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 279-92. Rules. Toledo, St. Louis, and Western Clover Leaf System
    - Toledo, St. Louis, and Western Clover Leaf System, 1921-1924 (Box 375, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 279-93. Rules. Camas Prairie Railroad
    - Mediation Case, 1964-1966 (Box 375, Folder 13)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1953 (Box 375, Folder 14)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 375, Folder 15)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 375, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 279-94. Rules. Central Freight Association
    - Central Freight Association, 1921 (Box 375, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 279-95. Rules. Peoria and Perkin Union Railway Company
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 375, Folder 18)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 375, Folder 19)
    - Peoria and Perkin Union Railway Company, 1936-1937 (Box 375, Folder 20)
    - Peoria and Perkin Union Railway Company, 1921-1926 (Box 375, Folder 21)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1956 (Box 375, Folder 22)
    - Peoria and Perkin Union Railway Company, 1938-1952 (Box 375, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 279-98. Rules. Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 375, Folder 24)
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad, 1955 (Box 376, Folder 1)
    - 1952-1954 (Box 376, Folder 2)
    - 1945-1952 (Box 376, Folder 3)
    - Arbitration Proceeding. Volumes 1-5, 1955 (Box 376, Folder 4)
      January-March 1955.
    - Arbitration Proceeding. Volumes 6-9, 1955 (Box 376, Folder 5)
    - Arbitration Proceeding. Volumes 10-13, 1955 (Box 376, Folder 6)
    - Arbitration Proceeding. Volumes 14-17, 1955 (Box 376, Folder 7)
    - Arbitration Proceeding. Volumes 18-20, 1955 (Box 376, Folder 8)
    - Arbitration Proceeding. Volumes 21-24, 1955 (Box 377, Folder 1)
    - Arbitration Proceeding. Volumes 25-28, 1955 (Box 377, Folder 2)
    - Arbitration Proceeding. Volumes 29-32, 1955 (Box 377, Folder 3)
    - Brief, 1955 (Box 377, Folder 4)
    - Brief, 1955 (Box 377, Folder 5)
    - Arbitration-Employee and Carrier Exhibits, 1955 (Box 377, Folder 6)
    - Arbitration Work File (Box 377, Folder 7)
    - Rules Adopted, 1954 (Box 377, Folder 8)
    - 1944-1947 (Box 377, Folder 9)
    - 1930-1943 (Box 377, Folder 10)
    - Vacations, 1942-1948 (Box 377, Folder 11)
    - Vacation Dispute, 1945-1948 (Box 377, Folder 12)
    - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad, 1921-1928 (Box 377, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 279-99. Rules. Boston and Maine Railroad
    - Boston and Maine Railroad, 1952-1960 (Box 378, Folder 1)
    - Stabilization of Employment, 1959 (Box 378, Folder 2)
    - Stabilization of Employment, 1958 (Box 378, Folder 3)
    - Union Shop, 1960 (Box 378, Folder 4)
    - Organization of Employment, 1958 (Box 378, Folder 5)
    - Employment Reductions, 1958-1959 (Box 378, Folder 6)
    - Boston and Maine Railroad, 1951-1952 (Box 378, Folder 7)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1950 (Box 378, Folder 8)
    - Vacation Dispute, 1948-1949 (Box 378, Folder 9)
    - Vacations, 1942-1949 (Box 378, Folder 10)
    - Boston and Maine Railroad, 1947-1948 (Box 378, Folder 11)
    - 279-99 (a). Boston and Maine Railroad, 1942-1947 (Box 378, Folder 12)
    - Rules Revision, 1942 (Box 378, Folder 13)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 378, Folder 14)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1949-1952 (Box 378, Folder 15)
    - Arbitration, 1947 (Box 378, Folder 16)
    - Boston and Maine Railroad, 1946-1952 (Box 378, Folder 17)
    - Boston and Maine Railroad, 1948 (Box 378, Folder 18)
    - Rules Revision. A-1128, 1942-1944 (Box 378, Folder 19)
    - General, 1933-1945 (Box 379, Folder 1)
    - Boston and Maine Railroad, 1923-1929 (Box 379, Folder 2)
    - Boston and Maine Railroad, 1921-1922 (Box 379, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 279-100. Rules. Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio
    - Union Shop, 1951-1955 (Box 379, Folder 4)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 379, Folder 5)
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio, 1953-1957 (Box 379, Folder 6)
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio, 1949-1952 (Box 380, Folder 1)
    - Vacations, 1944-1950 (Box 380, Folder 2)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1949-1950 (Box 380, Folder 3)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 380, Folder 4)
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio, 1948 (Box 380, Folder 5)
    - General, 1947 (Box 380, Folder 6)
    - General, 1945-1946 (Box 380, Folder 7)
    - General, 1943-1944 (Box 380, Folder 8)
    - Arbitration Transcript, 1944 (Box 380, Folder 9)
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio, 1932-1942 (Box 380, Folder 10)
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio, 1921-1929 (Box 380, Folder 11)
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio, 1943-1946 (Box 380, Folder 12)
    - Rules Division, 1940 (Box 380, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 279-101. Rules. Atlanta Joint Terminal
    - General, 1952-1955 (Box 381, Folder 1)
    - Atlanta Joint Terminal, 1942-1952 (Box 381, Folder 2)
    - Atlanta Joint Terminal, 1926-1941 (Box 381, Folder 3)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 381, Folder 4)
    - Vacations, 1950 (Box 381, Folder 5)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 381, Folder 6)
    - Atlanta Joint Terminal, 1944-1945 (Box 381, Folder 7)
    - Atlanta Joint Terminal, 1921 (Box 381, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 279-102. Rules. Texas Pacific-Missouri Pacific Terminal
    - Texas Pacific-Missouri Pacific Terminal, 1946-1954 (Box 381, Folder 9)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 381, Folder 10)
    - Mediation Case, 1960-1961 (Box 381, Folder 11)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 381, Folder 12)
    - Vacations, 1942-1947 (Box 381, Folder 13)
    - Texas Pacific-Missouri Pacific Terminal, 1929-1945 (Box 381, Folder 14)
    - Texas Pacific-Missouri Pacific Terminal, 1921 (Box 381, Folder 15)
    - Texas Pacific-Missouri Pacific Terminal, 1951-1953 (Box 381, Folder 16)
    - Texas Pacific-Missouri Pacific Terminal, 1940-1945 (Box 381, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 279-103. Rules. Long Island Railroad
    - General, 1964 (Box 381, Folder 18)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1961 (Box 381, Folder 19)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 382, Folder 1)
    - General, 1962-1963 (Box 382, Folder 2)
    - General, 1961-1962 (Box 382, Folder 3)
    - General, 1957-1961 (Box 382, Folder 4)
    - Long Island Railroad, 1949-1956 (Box 382, Folder 5)
    - Long Island Railroad, 1935-1936 (Box 382, Folder 6)
    - Long Island Railroad, 1946-1949 (Box 382, Folder 7)
    - Long Island Railroad, 1937-1945 (Box 382, Folder 8)
    - Vacations, 1942-1946 (Box 382, Folder 9)
    - Long Island Railroad, 1921 (Box 382, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 279-104. Rules. Central Railroad of New Jersey
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey, 1937-1944 (Box 382, Folder 11)
    - General, 1945-1956 (Box 382, Folder 12)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 383, Folder 1)
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey, 1938-1951 (Box 383, Folder 2)
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey, 1934-1936 (Box 383, Folder 3)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1949 (Box 383, Folder 4)
    - Vacations, 1942-1948 (Box 383, Folder 5)
    - Tug Dispatchers, 1946-1947 (Box 383, Folder 6)
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey, 1921-1925 (Box 383, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 279-105. Rules. Louisiana Railroad and Navigation Company
    - Miscellaneous Grievances, 1921-1929 (Box 383, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 279-106. Rules. Denver Union Terminal Railway Company
    - Red Caps and Ushers, 1953-1954 (Box 383, Folder 9)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 383, Folder 10)
    - Strike Clippings, 1956 (Box 383, Folder 11)
    - Red Caps, 1951 (Box 383, Folder 12)
    - Denver Union Terminal Railway Company, 1936-1953 (Box 383, Folder 13)
    - Denver Union Terminal Railway Company, 1956-1959 (Box 383, Folder 14)
    - Red Caps, 1939-1946 (Box 383, Folder 15)
    - Denver Union Terminal Railway Company, 1938-1946 (Box 383, Folder 16)
    - Clerks, 1951-1954 (Box 383, Folder 17)
    - 40 Hour Week, 1948-1951 (Box 383, Folder 18)
    - Denver Union Terminal Railway Company, 1922-1923 (Box 383, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 279-107. Rules. Houston Belt and Terminal
    - Mediation Case, 1966-1967 (Box 383, Folder 20)
    - 1958 Rules Movement (Box 383, Folder 21)
    - Houston Belt and Terminal, 1921-1922 (Box 383, Folder 22)
    - Union Shop, 1951-1954 (Box 383, Folder 23)